Clark Narvas

clark@narvas.co.uk | 07711939611 | by.clarknarvas.com

Profile

I'm a resilient and creative individual who produces many types of digital media to create lasting, positive change.

My interest in technology sparked from the iPad my parents gifted me when I was nine years old and the family computer. I used them to learn programming languages and creative media skills through online communities.

I know several programming, scripting and database languages: **HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, SQL, PHP and Ruby.** I've used these skills to bring value to others in ethical organisations and political campaigns. **My work is defined as a proficient organiser who is efficient and delivers quality work.**

Outside of my passion for technology, I am enthusiastic about helping people and building connections.

As Assistant Head Student at The Sheffield College Sixth Form Student Council, I manage Council meetings, assign tasks to a team of seven deputies, organise events (often with a charity focus) and liaise with teachers and students. I've also had the opportunity to talk to prospective students and present the welcome presentation on Open Evenings.

Education

A Levels at The Sheffield College September 2021 - August 2022 (Predicted Grades): Politics - A, Computer Science - A, Media Studies - B GCSEs at Tapton School August 2021: 9 GCSEs including Maths - 5, English Lang/Lit - 6, Computer Science - 6

Work Experience

Social Media & Communications: Crookes & Crosspool Labour Party - Developing websites and social media (June 2021 - Present) // Volunteer Work

I use video, audio and code to create social media and web content for Crookes and Crosspool Labour Party's social media channels. **During my** time in this role, I co-ordinated the successful digital campaign for Minesh Parekh for City Council which won on a mandate of 37.5%

- I acquired responsibility for all stages, from coding the website and SEO to designing branding, filming campaign material and posting social media posts.
- The website was built from the ground up for accessibility using HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS and Ruby. A static site generator called Jekyll acted as the backend, as it's known for fast compilation, serving speeds, and low maintenance costs.
- The website digitalised analogue campaign tactics, allowing 55+ volunteers from across the city to sign up and get involved.
- · By the end of the campaign, the social media posts gathered 86,000+ engagements across all social media platforms.
- Crookes & Crosspool elected Minesh Parekh by a mandate of 37.5% (+4.8), one of two Labour gains in Sheffield of the night.
- The experience of co-ordinating a significant part of a political campaign, alongside balancing my first year of A Level, gave
 me the organisational, problem-solving and communication skills vital when working under a fast-paced organisation.

Computer Science A Level Project: Luna Task Management Application

(2022) // Computer Science A Level Coursework

My A Level Computer Science coursework is a gamified task management web application called Luna Planner that centres around a virtual cat.

- I conducted focus group and surveys with the target stakeholders during the idea generation phase, interviewing seven students.
- Before the coding phase, I designed the software structure by creating UI prototypes, developing database relationships and planning classes.
- The final application runs on web technologies: HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL and JavaScript to ensure it's accessibility across devices.
- It features a points-based badge system and user accounts.

Digital Media Assistant: Sheffield City Council: Graphic Design and Video Creation

(June 2022 - December 2022) // Unpaid Placement

During my Sheffield City Council placement in June 2022, I was Digital Media Assistant for the Employment and Skills Service.

- I produced video case studies for job fairs, designed posters and managed event promotion on Eventbrite.
- I worked effectively across three teams, delivering on time and creating shared folders where peers could upload clips and resources.

Skills

Programming, Database and Markdown Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby, Python, SQL

Design and Video Production

Adobe After Effects, OBS Studio, Hitfilm Express, Photoshop

Soft skills

Project management, Organisation, Communication, Public speaking

Hobbies and Interests

Technology, creative media, journalling, meditating, exercising

Other notable experience

2018 - Launched 'Tech Byte', a short-form technology podcast

2019 - Completed Big Data course by WANdisco

2019 - Launched my blog at <u>ClarkNarvas.com</u>

2020 - Volunteered at Mozilla Support Forums

2020 - Social Media & Communications Officer at Labour Nexus

2021 - Student Union Representative for A Level Politics

2022 - Assistant Head Student at The Sheffield Sixth Form

References: Available upon request